scriptznull.nl 2018-09-23

# Privacy Policy | Scripts Nulled | ScriptzNull.NL

****  
Your privacy is important to us, and maintaining your trust and confidence is one of our highest priorities. We respect your right to keep your personal information confidential and understand your desire to avoid unwanted solicitations. A recent law change requires us (along with banks, brokerage houses, and other financial institutions) to disclose our Privacy Policy to you – which we are more than happy to do. We hope that by taking a few minutes to read it, you will have a better understanding of what we do with the information you provide us and how we keep it private and secure.

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

At scriptznull.nl, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by scriptznull.nl and how it is used.

**A.Log Files**

Like many other Web sites, www.scriptznull.nl makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement around the site, and gather Demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**B.Cookies and Web Beacons**

scriptznull.nl does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**C.DoubleClick DART Cookie**

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on scriptznull.nl send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

ScriptzNull has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. ScriptzNulls privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers respective websites.

Published:
    Feb 1, 2018
Page Views:
    232

Turning cookies on makes it easier for you to browse the web. Cookies are files created by websites you’ve visited, which store information, like the language you prefer or profile information. At Scriptznull, we use cookies to improve the quality of our service. Check our Privacy Policy for more information about cookies. Okay More information
